A Guide to the Headquarters Papers of Brigadier-General John Forbes Relating to the Expedition against Fort Duquesne in 1758
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- "Extract of a Letter of ye 20th July 1758 from a Merchant at New York." Docketed: "Extracts from Letters from a merchant in N: York July 20th. 1758", 1758 July 20; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Raystown, Bouquet and Walter Steuart: "A Daily Return of the Troops under Command of Col: Henry Bouquet Camp near Rays Town..." Docketed: "A Daily Return of the Troops at Rays Town July 21st 1758", 1758 July 21; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Loudon, John Paine. "A Return of Part of the North Carolina Troops under the Command of Major Hugh Waddell from the time of their Embarkation to their arrival at Fort Loudon in Pensylvania ", 1758 July 21; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Johnson, Sir William Johnson to [Denny.] Docketed: "Copy Letter of Sr Wm Johnson of 21st July 1758", 1758 July 21; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Johnson. "Sir William Johnson 's Speech to the Delaware Indians living on the Ohio and those Parts, sent this Day by Joseph Peppy, a Delaware Indian." Docketed: "Copy Speech inclosed in Letter of Sr Wm Johnson of 21 July 1758", 1758 July 21; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Raystown, Daniel Clark. "A Return of Provisions in Store at the Camp and Fort near Reas Town July the 21st. 1758." Docketed: "Return of provisions in Store at the Camp & Fort near Raestown 21st July 1758", 1758 July 21; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Loudoun, Hugh Waddell to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Waddell Fort Loudoun 21st July 1758", 1758 July 21; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Jacob Gooding. "A Report of the State of Jacob Gooding's Company given at Fort Loudon July 22. 1758", 1758 July 22; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Loudon, Richard Wells to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Majr. Wells Fort Loudoun 22 July 1758", 1758 July 22; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Letters Mr. Peters Philadelphia 22d July 1758 one the 29th", 1758 July 22; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes, 1758 July 22; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Philadelphia July 22d 1758", 1758 July 22; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Bouquet's Camp, [Raystown], James Glen to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Glenn Raystown July 22d 1758", 1758 July 22; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Hunters Fort, Andrew Finley to John Armstrong, Carlisle, 1758 July 22; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Lake George, Abercromby to Forbes, 1758 July 23; LS, 5 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Allen, Jacob Orndt to Denny. Docketed: "Copy letter of Major Orndt to Governor Denny of the 24th July 1758", 1758 July 24; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, George Morton. "A Return of the number of Waggons Loaded by Mr. Hoops from the 4th to 25th Inst", 1758 July 25; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Loudon, John Armstrong to Forbes, Carlisle. Docket: "Letter Colo. Armstrong Fort Loudoun 25th July 1758", 1758 July 25; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Copies of letters from George Armstrong to Bouquet. July 25, Edmund's Swamp; July 26, Kickenepaulins; July 27, "Extract of another Letter from Do: at Do:"; July 29, "Extract of another Letter," July 30, "Extract of another Letter," Docketed: "Intelligences receiv'd from Major Armstrong", 1758 July 25-30; 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Edmond's Swamp, George Armstrong to Bouquet. Docketed: "Letter Majr Armstrong to Colo. Bouquet Edmonds Swamp 25th July 1758", 1758 July 25; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Col. Bouquet's Camp, Raystown. James Glen to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Glenn Raystown July 26th 1758", 1758 July 26; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- "Ordnance Stores & Tools at Fort Frederick..." Docketed: "Return of Ammunition Stores & Forrage at Ft. Frederick July 26, 1758", 1758 July 26; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- David Ross, Fort Frederick. "The contracton for Victualling..." Docketed: " Fort Frederick Maryland The Contracton for Victualling with David Ross for Carriage of 36,484 Rations, July 26 1758 £ 288-6-1 Curry", 1758 July 26; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Denny to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Denny Philadelphia 28th July 1758", 1758 July 28; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Pennsylvania, Jacob Orndt. "Report of the Severil Detachments of the Pensylvania Regement a Foot Commanded by his Execelency Genral Forbes and are Stationd on the East Said of Susquanha July 28th 1758." Docketed: "Report of the Troops East Said of Susquanha", 1758 July 28; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Peters to [Forbes?]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Philadelphia 28th July 1758", 1758 July 28; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Conrad Weiser. Docketed: "Copy Letter Mr. Richard Peters to Colonel Weiser 28th. July 1758", 1758 July 28; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Richard Peters to [Forbes], 1758 July 29; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Brunswick, Cape Fear, Arthur Dobbs to [Forbes?] Docketed: "Letter Governr. Dobbs Brunswick Cape Fear 31st July 1758", 1758 July 31; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Johnston, Dalrymple to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Dalrymple Fort Johnson No. Carolina 1st August 1758", 1758 August 1; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown, Daniel Clark. "A Return of Provisions in Store at the Camp and Fort near Rays Town August the 1st 1758" Docketed: "Return of provisions in Store at Raystown 1st Augt. 1758", 1758 August 1; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Carlisle. Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Stores belonging to the Crown at Carlisle August y. 1st 1758." Docketed: "A Return of Stores at Carlisle 1st August. 1758", 1758 August 1; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- [Raystown], Edward Biddle. "King's Stores" Docketed: "Return of the King's Stores 1. August 1758", 1758 August 1; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown. "Account of sundrys remaining in his Majestys Stores at Rays Town or the Ballances taken from Edward Biddle s return to the 1st of August 1758" Docketed: "An Acct. of the Balls of Stores remaining at Raystown taken from John Biddle 's return 1st Augt. 1758", 1758 August 1; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Augusta, Levi Trump to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Trump Fort Augusta 1st August 1758", 1758 August 1 (?); LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Camp at Lake George, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Genl. Abercromby Lake George 2d August 1758", 1758 August 2; LS, 6 p. (Box Box 6)
- Albany, Richard Huck to [Forbes?] Docketed: "Letter Doctr. Huck Albany 2d Augt 1758", 1758 August 2; AL, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Augt. 2d 1758", 1758 August 2; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Jacob Orndt to Forbes, Raystown. Docket: "Letter Major Orndt Philadelphia Augt. 2d 1758", 1758 August 2; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Camp near Fort Cumberland, Byrd to [Forbes.] Docketed: "Letter Colo. Byrd Fort Cumberland 3d Augt. 1758", 1758 August 3; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Greenwich, Gilbert McAdam to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. McAdam Greenwich 3d Augt. 1758", 1758 August 3; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Phila., Thomas Bond to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Bond Philadelphia 3d Augt. 1758", 1758 August 3; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Carlisle, Adam Hoops to Forbes. "A Calculation of Provisions now in store at sundry Places, and the Time it will serve Six Thousand Men." Docketed: "Calculation of provisions in Store and the Time it will serve 6,000 men Carlisle 4th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 4; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Camp at Lake George, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Genl. Abercromby Lake George 5th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 5; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia. "At a Conference with the Indians in the Council Chamber at Philadelphia August the 5th. 1758." Docketed: "Copy Conferences with the Indians at Philadelphia 5th August 1758", 1758 August 5; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Augusta, Levi Trump to Forbes, Raystown. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Trump Fort Augusta Augt. 5th 1758", 1758 August 5; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- [Camp at Lake George], "List of Commissions," Docketed: "List of Commissions", 1758 August 5; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Paxton, John Harris to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Harris Paxton 6th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 6; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Littleton, Robert Eastburn to Commanding Officers at Loudoun. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Eastburn Fort Littleton 6th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 6; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Augusta, Levi Trump to Forbes, Raystown. Docket: "Letter Mr. Trump Fort Augusta 6th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 6; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Loudoun. Ourry to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Ourry Fort Loudoun 6th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 6; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Burlington. "At a Council held at Burlington Monday Augst: 7th 1758", 1758 August 7; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown, Draper [S.] Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Provisions in Store at Ray's Town and Carlisle with a Calculation how long it will serve Six Thousand Men." Docketed: "Return of provisions in Store at Raystown and Carlisle, with a Calculation how long it will serve 6000 men", 1758 August 7; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Edward Biddle. "King's Stores" Docketed: "Return of the King's Stores 8th. August 1758", 1758 August 8; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown, Daniel Clark to Bouquet. "A Return of Provisions in Store at the Fort near Rays Town August the 8th. 1758" Docketed: "A Return of provisis in Store at Raystown 8th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 8; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Camp at Raystown, James Glen to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Glenn Raestown Augt. 8th 1758", 1758 August 8; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
  Enclosed: Ms., "Rattle Snakes Faisants..."
- Raystown, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Sir John St Clair Raystown 8th August 1758", 1758 August 8; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Loudoun, Ourry to Forbes. Docketed: "Lieut. Oury from Fort Loudoun 9th August 1758 50 Indians Marching from Reastown", 1758 August 9; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
  In French.
- Camp at Kickenapauling's, George Armstrong to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Majr. Armstrong Camp at Kickeny Pallins 9th August 1758", 1758 August 9; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Denny to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Denny Philadelphia 10th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 10; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown, Thomas Hutchins to Forbes. "A Return of the Number of Forces served with Provisions at Reas Town, and of the time they are served for" Docketed: "Return of provisions Served to the Forces at Raestown 10th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 10; MsS, 2 p. (Box Oversize)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Philadelphia 10th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 10; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Philadelphia 10th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 10; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Carlisle, Forbes to Abercromby. Docketed: "Copy Answer Letter to Genl. Abercromby Carlisle 11th August 1758", 1758 August 11; LS (draft), 6 p. (Box Box 6)
  Corrections and additions in Forbes' handwriting.
- Edward Biddle. "King's Stores" Docketed: "Return of King's Stores 11 August 1758", 1758 August 11; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Raystown, Andrew Bay to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Bay Raystown 11th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 11; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, Francis Campbell to Forbes. Docketed: "Petition Frans. Campbell Shippensbourg 12th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 12; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Greenwich, Gilbert McAdam to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. McAdam Greenwich 13th August 1758", 1758 August 13; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, Adam Hoops to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Hoops Shippensbourg 13th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 13; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg. "Memorandum of the Fort at Shippenburg August: 13th: 1758." Docketed: "Memorandum of Fort Shippenburg Augst: 13th 1758", 1758 August 13; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Joshua Howell. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Mr. Howell Shippensburg 15 Augt. 1758", 1758 August 15; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to "Gentlemen" Docketed: "Copy Letter to the Magistrates and Gentlemn. in Lancaster, Bucks, Northhampton, and Philadelphia Counties 15th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 15; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, Forbes to Fauquier. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Gover. Fauquier Ship- pensbourg 16th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 16; ALS (draft), 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, Forbes to Dobbs. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Governr. Dobbs Shippensbourg 16th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 16; ALS (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to William H. Lyttelton. Docketed: "Letter to Governr. Littleton Shippensburg 16th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 16; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Loudoun, James Grant to Forbes, Shippensburg. Docketed: "Letter Major Grant Fort Loudoun 16th August 1758", 1758 August 16; ALS, 3 p. (Box Oversize)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Edmund Atkin. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Mr. Atkins Shippensbourg 16th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 16; AL (draft), 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Frederick, Sharpe to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Sharp Fort Frederick 18th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 18; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Greenwich, Gilbert McAdam to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Mc.Adam Greenwich 20th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Augusta, Levi Trump to Forbes, Raystown. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Trump Fort Augusta 20th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- "The examination of Jobi Chillaway, taken at Fort Augusta by Levi Trump. " Docketed: "Examination of Job Chilaway ", 1758 ca August 20; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Fort Frederick, Sharpe to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Sharp Fort Frederick 21st Augt 1758", 1758 August 21; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Sharpe. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Governr. Sharp Shippensbourg 23d Augt. 1758", 1758 August 23; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Philadelphia, Joshua Howell to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Howell Philadelphia 23 Augt. 1758", 1758 August 23; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Howell. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Mr. Howell Shippensbourg 26th Augt. 1758", 1758 August 26; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to David Ross. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Doctor Ross Shippensburg 28th August 1758", 1758 August 28; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, Francis Halkett. "A General Sketch of the number of Troops under the Command of Brigadier General Forbes." Docketed: "A Sketch of the number of Troops under the Commd of Brigadier Gen'l Forbes 1st September 1758", 1758 September 1; MsS, 2 p. (Box Oversize)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Sharpe. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Governr. Sharp Shippensbourg 3d Septr. 1758", 1758 September 3; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Shippensburg, [Forbes] to Abercromby. Docketed: "Copy Letter Genl. Abercromby Shippensbourg 4th Sepr. 1758", 1758 September 4; L (copy), 6 p. (Box Box 6)
- [Loyalhanna], Bouquet to François LeMarchand de Ligneris. Also includes: (1) "Copy of the Order given to Ensn. Blane... Sewp 19, 1758," (2) "Copy of the Governor of Fort DuQuesne's Letter to Col Bouquet... 22d 7ber 1758," (3) "Copy of Major Grants Letter (in French, with 'Liste des Officiers Anglois fait prisonnaires...')," and (4) "Copy of Col Bouquets Answer to the Governor of Fort DuQuesne 24th Septr. 1758." Docketed: "Copy of Colo. Bouquet's Letter to the Governr. of Fort Duquesne. 19th Septemr. 1758", 1758 September 19 -24; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 6)
- Albany, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Genl. Abercromby Albany 1st Novemr. 1758", 1758 November 1; LS, 7 p. (Box Box 7)
- New York, Jeffery Amherst to Forbes. Docketed: "From Sir Jeffery Amherst to Brig Gen Forbes", 1759 February 4; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 7)
- Philadelphia, John Inglis to Forbes, 1759 February 5; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- Capt. Ward. "A Report of Captain Ward sent to Reconnoitre the Road to the Westward" Docket: "Report of Captain Ward's", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Oversize)
- Albany, Matthew Clerk to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Mr. Clark Engineer Albany", no date; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Calculation of Oats for 400 Tames allowing 4 Horses to each Tame & to every Tame Six Gallons of Oats p Day...", no date; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Calculation of Oats for 400 Tames each Tame 4 horses & Six Gallons of Oats to every Tame p day..." Docketed: "Calculation of Oats for 400 Horses & Waggonage", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Pittsboro. "A Calculation showing the Expense of supporting an Army of 100 men at Pittsboro for 28 days", no date; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Explanation of an order of March for four thousand Infantry & one hundred & thirty Light men & guides", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Explanation to the Plan of the line of Battle", no date; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- "... By Virtue of the Power and Authority ...." Docketed: "Form of a Warrant appointing a President of a General Court Martial", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "General Shirly Appointed the following persons...", no date; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- Forbes to [St. Clair]. Docketed: "Instructions for the Qr Mr. Generale in the Southern Provinces", no date; AL (draft), 4 p. (Box Box 7)
- "It is needless to sett forth...", no date; Ms, 5 p. (Box Box 7)
  Summary of military strategy.
- John Fraser. "A List of Guides Employed in His Majesties Service." Docketed: "List of Guides", no date; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Forbes, "That Colonel Forbes, from his several purchases in the Army...", no date; AMs, 5 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Memorandum That Colonel Forbes from his several purchases...", no date; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
  Another draft of previous item.
- "Memorandums of Major Halketts" Docketed: "Memorandums of Major of Brigade Halketts ....", no date; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- Philadelphia, W. Smith to James Glen. Docketed: "Mr. Smith to Govr. Glen", [no date] "Tuesday 2.P.M"; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Capt. Bosomworth", [no date] "Thursday noon"; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Capt. Bosomworth", [no date] "Thursday evening"; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- Forbes. "The more that one thinks upon the nationale surface of North America...", no date; AMs, 10 p. (Box Box 7)
- "List of the Ships intended for the Expedition Vizt.", no date; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Waggons- whether bought or hired..." Docketed: "The Names and addresses of the several governours of the Southern Provinces", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Ordinance heavy Brass mounted..." Docketed: "Artillery", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "The Pennsylvania Regiment consisting of Three Battallions..." Docketed " Pennsylvania Regiment ", no date; Ms, 8 p. (Box Box 7)
- "A Provision Calculation for 6,000 men, from one to Twelve Weeks, allowing them 3 days Beef and 4 days Pork p week...." Docketed: "Calculation of Provisions for 6000", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Rough Plan of Fort de Quesne such as it was before it was demolish'd." Docketed: "Rough Plan of Fort du Qesnen", no date; Ms (Box Oversize)
- List of equipment with cost for a trooper. Docketed: "Saddles for the Light Horse ", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Places for Magazines Between Lancaster & Will's Creek or Fort Cumberland " Docket: "Magazines, Convoys, Rafts, Roads", no date; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- Richard Smith. "This is to Certifie..." Docketed: "Intelligence Smith Interpreter", no date; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "To his Excellency Horatio Sharpe Esqr: Governor and Commander in Chief in and over the Province of Maryland. The Petition of Edward Lloyd Esqr: of Talbot County...", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Numbers and location of military units in North America, "Nova Scotia, Royall...", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Troops destined for the Ohio, Fort du Quesne or other operations to the Southward" Docketed: "Distribution of the troops for the South West Expedition", no date; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- "Upon the firing of three cannon...", no date; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 7)
  Order of march.
- Forbes to. Docketed: "Munsters Company of Grenadrs in the 1st Battalion a fitt man properly employed for a Spy", no date; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Forbes to [ William Pitt ], no date; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Charles Rohr: "The Distance from Raystown to the Top of the Allegheny. " Docket: "Return by Mr. Rohr", no date; Ms (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Forbes to John Dagworthy. Docketed: "Copy Brigdr. Forbes to Capt. Dagworthy", no date; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to "My Lord", no date; AL (draft), 1 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to "Sir", "I did myself the honour to write you...", no date; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to "Sir", no date; L (draft), 4 p. (Box Box 7)
  Another draft of previous enrtry
- New York, [Forbes] to the Duke of B[edfor]d. Docketed: "Copy Letter to the Duke of B-d. N: York", no date; AL (draft), 6 p. (Box Box 7)
- (in third person), Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "G: Ab: Approving my instructions to Sir J. St. Clair", no date; L, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to [Lord Home?]. "As your Lordship was so good as deliver my letter...", no date; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to [Lord Home?]. "As your Lordship was so good to me...", no date; AL (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- [Forbes] to [Duke of Cumberland?], no date; AL (draft), 1 p. (Box Box 7)
  Probably an early draft of the following letter.
- n.p., [Forbes] to [Duke of Cumberland?], no date; L (copy), 2 p (Box Box 7)
- Fort Loudoun, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Sir John St. Clair Fort Loudoun", [no date] "Wednesday morning"; L, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Albany, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Genll Abercrombie", [no date] Thursday 22nd; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 7)
- Lord Home to "Jock", n.y. December 28; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 7)